Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Local and Underground Press Serials TAM.758
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Frontlines: C. Petroni, San Francisco, CA, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Gidra: Gidra, Inc., Los Angeles, CA, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 10-14, Box 97, Folder 6)
- Gimme Shelter: 108, Newark, NJ, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- GLF Occasional: GLF Occasional, Jersey City, NJ, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Gold Coast Free Press: Gold Coast Free Press, Inc., Coconut Grove, FL, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Good Times: Good Times Commune, San Francisco, CA, 1969-1972 (Box 62, Folder 5-9)
- Grape: Grape, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 2-4, Box 19, Folder 1-12, Box 20, Folder 1-5)
- Grass Roots - La Voz del Harlem Este: Grass Roots - La Voz del Harlem Este, New York, NY, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Grass Roots of Indianapolis: Grass Roots Publishing Co., Indianapolis, IN, Undated (Box 68, Folder 6, Box 95, Folder 12-15)
- Grassroots Magazine: Grassroots Press, Youngstown, OH, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Greaser Comics: Half-Ass Press, New York, NY, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Great Flint Sit-Down Strike Against G.M.: Radical Education Project / Bay Area Radical Education Project, Ann Arbor, MI, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Great Speckled Bird: Atlanta Cooperative News Project, Atlanta, GA, Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Greensboro Sun: Greensboro Sun, Greensboro, NC, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- GSBA News: Greater Seattle Business Association, Seattle, WA, 1983-1984 (Box 92, Folder 19)
- Guardian Marketplace: New York, NY, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Guardian: Independent Radical Newsweekly: Guardian, New York, NY, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Guerilla: Mac - Pap Publishing Ltd., Toronto, Ontario, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Guinea Pig Zero: Robert P. Helms, Philadelphia, PA, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Gulf Coast Fish Cheer: Pensacola Co-op News Service c/o Universal Life Church, Pensacola, FL, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Hair: Hair, Minneapolis, MN, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- HAPOTOC news: HAPOTOC, Amsterdam, Holland, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- HAPOTOC/SIP Bulletin: Leeuwarden, Friesland, Holland, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Hard Times: East Cambridge Neighborhood Project, East Cambridge, MA, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Harlem Overheard: Harlem Children's Zone, Inc., New York, NY, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Harry: Dixie Peach Publishing, Baltimore, Maryland, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Harry: Atlantis Pub. Co., Baltimore, Md, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Hartford's Other Voice: Hartford's Other Voice, Hartford, CT, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Hat City Free Press: Hat City Free Press, Danbury, CT, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Hawaii Free Peoples Press: Hawaii Free Peoples Press, Haleiwa, HI, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Hearth and Home: Orange Judd and Co, New York, 1871 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Henderson Station: State College, PA, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Herald Tribune: Herald Tribune, Brooklyn, NY, Undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Heretic's Journal Bulletin: Heretic's Journal, Seattle, WA, 1984-1985 (Box 92, Folder 20)
- Heterodoxy: Center for the Study of Popular Culture, Studio City, CA, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 5, Box 95, Folder 3)
- Highway 13: Military Law Project / Highway 13, Odenton, MD, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Hiroshima/Nagasaki Week Reports: No Business as Usual, San Francisco, CA, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- History as Indoctrination: A Cititque of Palmer and Colton's History of the Modern World: Radical Historians Caucus, Somerville, MA, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Hobo News: n.p., 1945 (Box 97, Folder 21)
- Hooka: Humanitarian Order of Kosmic Awareness, Dallas, TX, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Huli: Huli, Honolulu, HI, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Hundred Flowers: Hundred Flowers, Minneapolis, MN, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Hunley Hemorrhoid Free Press: The Hunley Hemorrhoid, E Division USS Hunley, FPO, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Hunter / Gatherer: Crimeth Inc. Journey of Folklore and Folkwar, Oympia, WA, Undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Illuminations: Ed Bullins, Santa Fe, NM, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- In Struggle: In Struggle, San Jose, CA, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 26, Box 18, Folder 1)
- Incredible Bureaucrat: Incredible Bureaucrat, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Independent: The Independent, New York, NY, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 6, Box 70, Folder 5, Box 91, Folder 2-5)
- Independent: Expose Inc., New York, NY, 1961-1964 (Box 90, Folder 1-10)
- Independent Peoples Tribunal Newsletter: National Continuing Committee for an Independent Peoples Tribunal, Oakland, CA, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Indianapolis Free Press:Radical Pub. Co. of Ind., Inc., Indianapolis, IN, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Individualist: The Individualist Press, Denver, CO, 1890 (Box 92, Folder 21)
- Inner City Light: Inner City Light, New York, NY, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Inner City Press: Inner City Press, Bronx, NY, 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Insurgent: University of Oregon, Eugene, OR, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Intertribal News Service: Free Ranger Tribe, New York, NY, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Iowa City Oppressed Citizen: Iowa City Oppressed Citizen, Iowa City, IA, Undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Issues: St. Paul Dispatch / Pioneer Press, St. Paul, MN, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Joint Issue: Joint Issue, East Lansing, MI, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Journal: Journal, Rochester, NY, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Journal of Community Communications: Village Design, Berkeley, CA, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 22)
- Journey: Control, Conflict and Change, Detroit, MI, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Kaleidoscope: Kaleidoscope, Milwaukee, WI, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Kersplebedeb Catalog 2004: Kersplebedeb Publishing and Distribution, Montreal, Quebec, Canada (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Kew Forest Beacon: Kew-Forrest Club: American Labor Party, Queens, NY, 1958 (Box 92, Folder 23)
- Key Notes: Greater Homewood Community Corporation, Inc., Baltimore, MD, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- King Street Trolley: Weakly, Inc., Madison, WI, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- King Street Trolley: Liberation News Service, Madison, WI, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Kingsman: Brooklyn College CLAS, Brooklyn, NY, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Kudzu: Kudzu Mediaworks, Jackson, MS, 1970-1982 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- L.A. Catalyst: The L.A. Catalyst, Los Angeles, CA, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- L.A. Catalyst: Catalyst Collective, Los Angeles, CA, Undated (Box 83, Folder 5)
- L.E.S.A. Lower East Side Advocate: LEAS / Foto-Ready Advocate, New York, NY, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- L'Action Francais: Organe du nationalisme integral, Paris. France, 1937 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- L'Idiot International: L'Idiot International, Paris, France, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 9, Box 42, Folder 13, Box 75, Folder 17)
- L'Idiot Liberté: L'Idiot Liberté, Paris, France, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- L'unique et son ombre:, Paris, France, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- La Actualidad Espanola: La Actualidad Espanola, Barcelona, Spain, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- La Causa: National Brown Beret Organization, Compton, CA, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- La Gaceta chibcha: La Gaceta Chibcha, New York, NY, 1969-1970 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- La Libre Parole: Grande Imp., Paris, France, 1937 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Lancaster Independent Press: Lancaster Independent Press, Inc., Lancaster, PA, 1972-1984 (Box 45, Folder 6-7)
- Las Vegas Free Press: J.A. Carruth, Las Vegas, NV, 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Le Chronic: Le Chronic, Inc., Roxbury, MA, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Le Matin De Paris: Claude Perdriel, Paris, France, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Leader: Leader, 1933 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- League News: United League of Mississippi, Holly Springs, MS, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Lehigh Valley Review: Lehigh Valley Review, Allentown, PA, 1933 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- LI Action: Progressive Coalition: Citizen Action on Long Island, Amityville, NY, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Liberated Guardian: Liberated National Publication / The Liberated Guardian, New York, NY, 1970-1973 (Box 32, Folder 1-5, Box 45, Box 51, Folder 4, Box 73, Box 95)
- Liberation Struggle: Center of Writers and Journalists of the Exploited World, London, England, 1972 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Lincoln Avenue Ambush: Lincoln Avenue Ambush / The Seed, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
- LIP: The Lancaster Independent Press, Lancaster, PA, 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 12, Box 43, Folder 1-5)
- London Broadsheet: Kenneth Coutts-Smith, London, England, 1955 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Long Beach Free Press: Long Beach Free Press, Long Beach, CA, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Long Beach Rising Star: Long Beach Unified School District, Long Beach, CA, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Long Island Daily Press: Advance Publication, Queens, NY, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Long Island Free Press: Coming Together, Inc., Westbury, NY, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 14, Box 47, Folder 4)
- Long Island Free Press: Coming Together, Inc., Westbury, NY, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Lower East Side Rose: Rose News Service, New York, NY, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Lumpen Times: Lumpen Times Inc., Chicago, IL, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Madison Kaleidoscope: Electric Teradactyl Transit Authority, Ltd., Madison, WI, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Magazine: n.p., New York, NY, circa 1980s (Box 92, Folder 24)
- Manchester Guardian: Manchester Guardian and Evening News, Ltd, Manchester, England, 1964-1965 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Manhattan Spirit: News Communications, Inc., New York, NY, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 9, Box 60, Folder 10, Box 95)
- Manhattan Tribune: William F. Haddad and Roy Innis / Newswrite Press, Incorporated, New York, NY, 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 7, Box 83, Folder 4, Box 95, Folder 2)
- Massachusetts Sun: Rand Avery & Co., Boston, MA, 1875 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Maverick:, Santa Clara, CA, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Maverick: Voice of the Santa Clara County Workers' Committee: Santa Clara County Workers' Committee, Santa Clara, CA, Undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
- MDS Newsletter: New Orleans Movement for a Democratic Society, New Orleans, La, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Mesechabe: The Journal of Surre(gion)alism: Center for Gulf South History and Culture, New Orleans, LA, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Metamorphosis: Red Sticks News Co-op, Little Rock, AR, Undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Metropolitan News: United Press Association, Los Angeles, CA, 1956 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Michigan Voice: The Michigan Voice, Inc., Burton, MI, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Mid-Valley Log: Rolling Log Collective, Salem, OR, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 2, Box 48)
- Midnight Special: Revolutionary Youth Movement, Racine, WI, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Midwest Anti-Fascist: The MAFNET Internal Bulletin, St. Paul, MN, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 25)
- Midwest Citizen: Bell Publications, Omaha, NE, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- miljoenen europese huisvrouwen zijn enthousiast de dooie mus: n.p., 1996 (Box 92, Folder 26)
- Milwaukee Review: Milwaukee Review, Milwaukee, WI, 1970-1983 (Box 34, Folder 9, Box 35, Box 63, Folder 8, Box 72, Folder 5)
- Milwaukee Sentinel: Milwaukee Sentinel, Milwaukee, WI, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Minding the Store: Earth Activities, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Minority Report: Minority Report, Dayton, OH, 1969-1970 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Modern Times: Modern Times Collective, Johnson City, NY, 1974-1976 (Box 42, Folder 9, Box 46, Folder 4, Box 63)
- Mole: People's Media Center, Boston, MA, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Mole: Students for a Democratic Society, Boston, MA, 1970-1971 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Moniebogue Press: Torope Publishers, Inc., Westhampton, NY, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- [More]: Rosebud Associates, Inc., New York, NY, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Mountain Liberator: Appalachian Mountain Youth Collective, Morgantown, WV, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Movement: Movement Press, San Francisco, CA, 1965-1970 (Box 25, Folder 7, Box 44, Folder 1-2, Box 48, Folder 5, Folder 8-9, Box 60, Folder 11, Box 70, Folder 8, Box 72)
- Movin' On Up: Movin' On Up, Cincinnati, OH, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Nebraska Biweekly Dispatch: Nebraska Dispatch, Lincoln, NE, 1974-1975 (Box 76, Folder 7-9)
- Neue Solidaritat: Verlag Schiersteiner, Wiesbaden, Germany, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- New Common Good: New Common Good, New York, NY, 1984-1988 (Box 76, Folder 6, Box 35, Folder 10, Box 95)
- New Indicator: University of California at San Diego, La Jolla, CA, 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 3, Box 95, Folder 11, Box 97)
- New Mexico Lobo: Board of Student Publications of the Associated Students of the University of New Mexico, Albuquerque, NM, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- New Morning: Columbia Free Press Corporation, Columbia, MO, 1970-1971 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- New Morning: New Morning Collective, Berkeley, CA, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 11)
- New Orleans News: New Orleans News Associates, New Orleans, LA, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- New Pages: New Pages Press, Grand Blanc, MI, 1980-1986 (Box 92, Folder 27)
- New Patriot: Johnny Appleseed Patriotic Publications, Chicago, IL, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- New Prairie Primer: Campus Publications, Cedar Falls, IA, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 15, Box 46, Folder 9)
- New River Free Press: New River Free Press, Blacksburg, VA, 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- New Unity: New Unity, Springfield, MA, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 20-21, Box 9, Folder 8, Box 46, Folder 13)
- A New World Rising: A New World Rising, Providence, RI, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- New York Ace: New York Ace, Inc., New York, NY, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 11, Box 31, Folder 10)
- New York Advocate: Urban Affairs Foundation, Inc., New York, NY, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- New York Daily Column and the New York Knickerbocker: New York Daily Column, Inc., New York, NY, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- New York Element: Arts Section of the Peace & Freedom Party of New York, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 12, Box 97, Folder 22-23)
- New York Free Press: New York Free Press, New York, NY, 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 14, Box 44, Folder 3, Box 60, Folder 13, Box 63, Folder 11-12)
- New York Free Press / Guardian: New York Free Press, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- New York Newsday: New York Newsday, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- New York RAT: New York RAT, New York, NY, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 10, Box 96, Folder 8, Box 97, Folder 12)
- New York Standard: New York Standard, New York, NY, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- New York World-Telegram and the Sun: New York World-Telegram Corporation, New York, NY, 1950 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- New Youth Connections NYC: Youth Communication / New York Center, Inc., New York, NY, 1985-1991 (Box 63, Folder 13, Box 72, Folder 8)
- Newpaper: The Newpaper, Lynn, MA, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- News from Nowhere: News from Nowhere, Dekalb, IL, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- News Notes: DC Gazette, Washington, DC, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Newsletter: Morningside Retirement & Health Services, Inc., New York, NY, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Newslette r: Sanity Now!, La Puente, CA, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 28)
- Newsletter: Westchester Chapter, United Nations Association of the United States of America, Westchester County, NY, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 29)
- Nihilist: Nihil Press, New York, NY, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- No Limits: Dream World Dragon Press, Madison, WI, 1976-1979 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- No Picinic: No Picinic, Vancouver, BC, Canada, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- NOLA Express: Southern Louisiana Media Corporation, New Orleans, LA, 1972-1973 (Box 76, Folder 5, Box 82, Folder 1-4)
- Noospaper: Noospaper, New York, NY/Westfield, NJ, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 26, Box 75, Folder 14)
- Norfolk Gorilla: Norfolk Gorilla, Norfolk, VA, 1972 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- North Carolina Anvil: North Carolina Independent Publishing Co., Durham, NC, 1968-1982 (Box 52, Folder 1-4, Box 53, Folder 1-5, Box 54, Box 55, Folder 1-6, Box 56, Box 57, Box 58, Box 59)
- North Country: North Country Publications, Portland, ME, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- North Country Press: North Country Press, Minneapolis, MN, Undated (Box 82, Folder 6)
- North Country Star: North Country Star, Burlington, VT, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Off the Hook: Missouri Prisoners' Labor Union/Black Unicorn Press, Kirksville, MO, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 30)
- Okanogan Natural News: G. Payton and R. Gillespie, Chesaw, WA, 1983-1987 (Box 5, Folder 27, Box 33, Folder 3)
- Oklahoma Observer: The Oklahoma Observer, Oklahoma City, OK, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Old Mole: Old Mole, Boston, MA, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 16, Box 70, Folder 9, Box 97, Folder 14)
- Old Mole: Old Mole, Cambridge, MA, 1968-1969 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Olklahoma Observer: Troy Enterprises, Co., Olkahoma City, OK, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 1-8)
- Omaha Kaleidoscope: Omaha Kaleidoscope, Omaha, NE, Undated (Box 81, Folder 5)
- On CUE: The Coalition for a United Elizabeth, Elizabeth, NJ, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- On The Move: Youth in Action, Detroit, MI, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- On The Move: On The Move, Bronx, NY, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- One Parent Family, The: Metrocenter YMCA, Seattle, WA, 1979 (Box 92, Folder 31)
- Open City: Open City, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Open City: Open City Press, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Oregon Times: New Oregon Publishers, Inc., Portland, OR, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Organ: Himalayan Watershed Properties, Inc., Berkeley, CA, Undated (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Other Paper: The Other Paper, New York, NY, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Other Voice: Other Voice, Shreveport, LA, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Outcry: Radical Student Union, Berkeley, CA, Undated (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Ovella Negra: n.p., Spain, circa 1980s (Box 92, Folder 32)
- Overseas Weekly Stateside: Overseas Media Corp., Oakland, CA, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Overthrow: Youth International Party, Information Service, New York, NY, 1973-1988 (Box 4, Folder 16, Box 44, Folder 6, Box 71, Folder 6-7)
- Overthrow: Youth International Party Information Service, New York, NY, circa 1980s (Box 93, Folder 1)
- OWL: Diana Johnstone, Paris, France, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Ozark Mountain Times: Ozark Mountain Times Collective and Friends, Fayetteville, AR, 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 16, Box 81, Folder 2)
- P.I.C. Times: The People's Independent Coalition, New Brunswick, NJ, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 17, Box 18, Folder 4)
- Pacific Tribune: West Coast edition, Canadian Tribune, Vancouver, BC, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Pacific Tribune: Pacific Tribune, Vancouver, BC, 1977-1985 (Box 76, Folder 3, Box 81, Folder 1)
- Papel Chicano: Mexican American Cultural Corporation, Houston, TX, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Paper: City College of New York, New York, NY, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Paper Tiger: Radical High-School Students' Publication: Paper Tiger, New York, NY, Undated (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Paradiso Fox: Paradiso Fox, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Park Press: The Crystal City News Staff, North Baltimore, OH, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Patriot: Sunshine Publications, Kalamazoo, MI, 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 1-3, Box 51, Folder 5-6)
- The Patriot: Patriot Party, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Penumbra: Porcine Software, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- People First: The People First/Dorchester Tenants Action Council, Dorchester, MA, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- People's Community News: People's Community Center, Dayton, OH, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- People's Herald: The People's Herald, New York, NY, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- People's News Service: People's News Service, Tucson, AZ, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- People's Voice: Communist Party of the United States, Chicago, IL, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- People's Voice: Communist Party of the United States, Ocean Hill-Brownsville, NY, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- People's Voice: Communist Party of the United States, Los Angeles, CA, 1965-1968 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- People's Voice: Central Vermont Community Action Council, Montpelier, VT, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- People's War: People's War, Philadelphia, PA, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- People's Weekly: Center for Black Development, Waterbury, CT, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Petal Paper: Petal Publishing Company, Petal, MS, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Petal Paper: Southeastern Publishing Co., Montgomery, AL / Petal, MS, 1963-1972 (Box 89, Folder 1-6)
- Philadelphia Free Press: Freedom Press Inc., Philadelphia, Pa, 1969-1973 (Box 88, Folder 6-7)
- Phoenix: Southern Student Organizing Committee, Nashville, TN, 1968-1969 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Pica Hielo: n.p., Mexico, circa 1980s (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Pitirre: Young Lords Organization, Chicago, IL, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Plain Dealer: Plain Dealer Collective, Philadelphia, PA, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- PM's Sunday Picture News: Newspaper PM, Inc., New York, NY, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Popular Reality: Popular Reality, Ann Arbor, MI, 1986-1987 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Port-Au-Prince Times: Herbert J. Morrison, Port-Au-Prince, Haiti, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Post Amerikan: Post Amerikan, Bloomington, IL, 1981-1987 (Box 30, Folder 1-4, Box 51, Folder 16)
- Prairie Dispatch: Prairie Dispatch Collective, Urbana, IL, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Prairie Fire: Michigan Free Press, Ann Arbor, MI, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Progressive Citizen: Progressive Citizens of America, New York, NY, 1948 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Progressive People's Power: Progressive People's Power, Harvey, IL, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Protean/Radish: Carolina Media Project, Chapel Hill, NC, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 9-10)
- Protos: Protos, Los Angeles, CA, 1970-1971 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Providence Free Press: Providence Free Press, Providence, RI, 1971 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Provincial Press Collective: Provincial Press Collective, Spokane, WA, 1970-1972 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Psych-Agitator: Stony Brook, RI, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 12)
- Psychologists for a Democratic Society Newspaper: Psychologists for a Democratic Society, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Pulp: Pulp Collective, Amherst, MA, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Quicksilver Times: Sixth Column, Washington, DC, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 18, Box 83, Folder 2)
- Radical Philosophy Association: Research Associates Foundation, Inc. - Progressive Action Center, Baltimore, MD, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Radical Philosophy Newsletter: Research Associates Foundation, Inc. - Progressive Action Center, Baltimore, MD, 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Radical Publications and Organizations: Liberation News Service, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Radical Rag: Ragged Edge Press, New York, NY, Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Radical Therapist: The Radical Therapist, Inc., West Somerville, MA, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Razor's Edge: Razor's Edge, Boston, MA, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Rebellion News: Rebellion Associates, Roxbury, MA, 1967-1968 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Rebirth: Real Live People, Inc., Phoenix, AZ, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Red Army: Red Army, Philadelphia, PA, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Red Balloon Magazine: Red Balloon Magazine, Brooklyn, NY, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Red Pencil: The Red Pencil, Boston, MA, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Red Star Express: Revolutionary Youth Movement, Milwaukee, WI, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Report from the West Side Progressive Forum: n.p., Brooklyn, NY, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Resistance: Documents and Analyses of the Illegal Front: Friends of Durruti, Vancouver, BC, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Resurrection: People's News Service: Ministry of Information, Tucson, AZ, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Revolution = Revolucion: Revolutionary Union, Chicago, IL, 1973-1977 (Box 67, Folder 1-4)
- Rhubard: Radical Humor Union Network: Rhubarb, Hoboken, NJ, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Richmond Chronicle: Richmond Chronicle, Richmond, VA, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Right On: Right On, Boston, MA, Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Rising Up Angry: Rising Up Angry, Chicago, IL, 1969-1975 (Box 15, Folder 1-11, Box 84, Folder 1-9, Box 16, Box 33, Folder 5-7, Box 42, Folder 8, Box 60, Folder 20, Box 85)